vangraaf.com 2015-12-21

# Privacy policy

### My store

Select your VAN GRAAF fashion store to display important information at a glance.

VAN GRAAF attaches high priority to the protection of your personal data and rights to confidentiality and privacy in the Internet. Please read our policy on data security. Our aim is to make clear to you how we handle personal details, which information we store and how we use it.

Generally, it is possible to visit our website without giving any personal details. Only information provided voluntarily to us will be used for the purpose you have given us the data (e.g. for answering a question you raised in the feedback form). Your data will not be transferred to third parties without your express consent and treated with utmost confidentiality. 

The use and processing of personal information will be handled in line with the Austrian data protection law. 

When you visit our website, or indeed any other website, certain data is automatically stored. To this extent, the name of your Internet service provider, the pages you visit, the website from which you have visited us and the date and duration of your visit will be stored. Your privacy and right to confidentiality are protected as individual users remain anonymous.

### Use of Google Analytics

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. In case of activation of the IP anonymization, Google will truncate/anonymize the last octet of the IP address for Member States of the European Union as well as for other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases, the full IP address is sent to and shortened by Google servers in the USA. On behalf of the website provider Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage to the website provider. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore you can prevent Google’s collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB). 

You can refuse the use of Google Analytics by clicking on the following link. An opt-out cookie will be set on the computer, which prevents the future collection of your data when visiting this website: Disable Google Analytics

Further information concerning the terms and conditions of use and data privacy can be found at [http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html) or at [https://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/policies/](https://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/policies/). Please note that on this website, Google Analytics code is supplemented by “gat._anonymizeIp();” to ensure an anonymized collection of IP addresses (so called IP-masking).

### Right of cancellation, RIGHT OF ACCESS

You are entitled to object the use of your data for purposes of advertising or of market- or opinion research at any time. Furthermore you have the right of access to stored personal information. Should you want to make use of either or both of these rights, please inform us per e-mail to: [info@vangraaf.com](mailto:info@vangraaf.com) or send us a letter to VAN GRAAF, Traungasse 14, A-1030 Vienna.

### Data security

VAN GRAAF feels responsible for protecting your privacy in the Internet. We take great care to update our Internet pages in accordance with the latest technical and organizational security measures in order to protect your personal details from illicit use or distribution to third parties.

### Cookies

Cookies are small parcels of text stored on the computer of the visitors of a website. While you visit our website we use cookies that will be deleted immediately if you close your browser. Cookies aim at ensuring our website is user friendly, effective and secure and making your visit of our website as comfortable as possible. Your browser should allow you to decide whether to accept cookies. More information on how to make your browser reject cookies you usually find in the help function of your browser.

### Statement on Processing of Online Job Applications

VAN GRAAF GmbH & Co. KG (VAN GRAAF) will process the personal data included in your online application mainly in order to deal with your application for its own recruiting purposes. Furthermore VAN GRAAF may transfer your online application to its associated companies*, which may then process it for their own recruiting purposes only. VAN GRAAF or its associated companies* may in certain cases also hand over your online application to service providers assisting them in sorting out appropriate candidates. For some vacancies on offer VAN GRAAF might also request you to send your online application directly to such a service provider. These service providers only act on behalf of VAN GRAAF respectively its associated companies* and are not allowed to use your data for any other purposes or transfer it to third parties. 

Please note that VAN GRAAF does not wish to receive via your CV or attached documents any information on special categories of personal data (which means information on your racial or ethnic origin, your political opinions, religious or philosophical convictions, union membership, health or sex life) and will not take this information into account when reviewing your application. However, if you should include such information in your online-application, you allow VAN GRAAF and its associated companies* to process this data along with your application. 

*

| 

 **VAN GRAAF** **GmbH Sp. k.**  
Ul. Kielbasnicza 32  
PL  50-109 Wroclaw  
Poland 

| 

**VAN GRAAF** **, k. s.**  
Ve Svahu 482/5  
CZ 140 00 Praha  
Czech Republic   
  
---|---|---  
| 

**VAN GRAAF** **Bt.**  
Andrássy út 121  
1062 Budapest  
Hungary 

| 

**VAN GRAAF GmbH & Co. KG**  
Zweigniederlassung Spreitenbach  
Industriestraße  
CH-8957 Spreitenbach  
  
| 

 **VAN GRAAF** **GmbH & Co. KG**  
Traungasse 14  
1030 Wien  
Austria 

| 

**Peek &Cloppenburg KG**  
Mönckebergstraße 8  
20095 Hamburg  
Germany  
  
### Questions and comments

Please e-mail us your questions and comments concerning data protection. The content of our policy statement may be updated from time to time in accordance with developments on the Internet. In order to find out about the latest position on security, you are advised to consult the content of these pages on a regular basis.
